Okay, guys, listen.
好，大家注意聽
Tomorrow, Emily gets married again.
明天是艾蜜莉再婚的日子
So try to really keep Ross' mind off of it.
我們要盡全力 轉移羅斯的注意力
Good idea.
對，好主意
Hey,man. What's up?
你怎麼了？
Just thinking about Emily getting married tomorrow.
正在想艾蜜莉明天結婚的事
Oh,Ross! Look,look!
羅斯，你看
What? Where?
看什麼？在哪裡？
Right over there! There! Look,look,look!
就在那兒啊，快看…
-What am I looking at? -Somebody help me out here.
你要我看什麼？ 誰來幫幫我啊
Hey!
你們好嗎？
Monica,sorry I didn't come by. I was out with Gary.
摩妮卡，抱歉我昨晚沒過去 我跟蓋瑞在一起
He let me ride around with him. We saw and prevented crimes.
他用警車載我去兜風 我們還阻止了一起犯罪
You got to go on a ride-along?
你可以坐警車去兜風？
-I want to go on a ride-along! -Me too!
我也要坐警車兜風 我也是
-Okay. -Yeah! Me too!
好啊 我也要
Really? You?
你真的要？
Yeah.
是啊
-Well,it's kind of dangerous. -Well,I like danger.
有點危險喔 我喜歡危險
-Okay, you guys free tonight? -Yeah!
好，你們今天晚上有空嗎？ 有…
You didn't say it was gonna be at nighttime.
今晚？你剛才沒說是在晚上
The One With the Ride-Along
本集播出：「搶救三明治」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I'm so glad you're home. We can finally organize these photos.
真高興你回家了 今晚總算能整理這些相片
Oh,thank God!
謝天謝地
Finally!
終於！
I've broken them down into categories.
我已經把照片分門別類
We got holidays, birthdays, candids....
有假日類、生日和偷拍
And I've cross-referenced them by subject.
我已經依照主題 做好了交叉搜尋
So if you're looking up,say...
好比你要找...
...birthdays and dogs, you get photo 152.
...生日和狗 就會找到152號相片
See?
你看
Oh,it's me and LePoo.
是我和拉普
Wow,I miss that dog.
我真懷念那條狗
You can also find him under "dog" and "dead."
你也能在狗和死亡項目之中 找到拉普
Great. Thanks.
太好了，多謝
Hand me that other box of photos. That's the last one.
把另一箱照片遞給我 那是最後一箱
Oops.
糟糕
Sorry.
對不起啦
Good thing you numbered them.
幸好你有寫上號碼，對吧？
I hadn't.
還沒
Photo 152 was a prototype.
152號相片是範例
Honey, it's okay. It's okay.
別難過…
How about I fix you a drink? Maybe a margarita?
我幫你弄杯喝的 瑪格莉特好嗎？
Ross has the blender.
果汁機在羅斯那裡
Everything's just falling apart.
一切都毀了
It's okay. I'll go to Ross', get the blender.
親愛的，不礙事 我去找羅斯拿果汁機
-You get the margarita stuff ready. -All right.
你先準備瑪格莉特的材料 好吧
His keys are in the drawer. Also,I need some cash.
他家鑰匙放在抽屜裡 我還需要一些現金
Want me to stop at the ATM?
你要我去自動櫃員機取嗎？
No. While you're at Ross', if you see any lying around.
不用，到羅斯家裡拿就好
-What? -What?
什麼？ 什麼？
I don't do that.
我不做那種事的
That was so cool,man. The way you leaned on that guy.
你逼問那傢伙的方式 真是太酷了
It is starting to get dark out there.
天色越來越黑了
He told you everything. You cracked him.
他什麼都招了 他對你毫不保留
He was the victim. They're usually pretty talkative.
對，他是受害者 他們通常都很多話
Okay, but it is officially nighttime.
好，正式進入夜晚了
-Want me to grab the berry for you? -It's called a cherry.
蓋瑞，要我幫你拿紅燈嗎？  這叫做「警燈」
It's called Chandler!
這叫做「警燈」
Okay,I got it.
買到了
This place makes the best sandwich in the world.
這家店做的三明治 世界第一
Does it have meatballs?
喬伊，裡頭有肉球嗎？
Oh,yeah.
沒錯
Melted cheese and marinara sauce?
有融化的起司 和大蒜番茄醬嗎？
Yep.
有
You can't eat that in my car.
那就不能在我的車上吃
Yeah,okay.
好吧
Even though my tax dollars paid for this car.
買這部警車的錢 我繳的稅也有一份
Your tax dollars?
你繳的稅？
Yeah,okay.
好啦（你繳的稅）
Wow,that sandwich smells good.
這個三明治還真香
Did I say you could smell it?
我有說你可以聞嗎？
I can't smell it?
聞個三明治都不行？
Half the taste is in the smell. You're sucking up all the taste units.
香味就佔去了好吃的一半 你把好吃都吸光了
Okay,I'll give them back.
好吧，還給你
What is so great about that sandwich?
這三明治到底棒在哪裡？
Imagine the best sex you ever had.
想想你做愛最爽的一次 好
-Are you thinking about Monica? -Yeah.
你想的是摩妮卡嗎？ 是啊
What's that like?
是什麼感覺？
Please don't be from a real dinosaur. Please,please.
拜託不要是真的恐龍
Please,please.
千萬不要…
"Made in Mexico." Yes!
墨西哥製造，好耶
Who would buy this?
誰會買這種東西？
Rach, it's me. Pick up!
瑞秋，是我，快接啊
What's up?
什麼事？
I need a few more things for the margaritas.
我做瑪格莉特還缺材料
I need some salt, some margarita mix and tequila.
我要鹽巴、瑪格莉特調汁 還有龍舌蘭酒
So all we had was ice?
我們家裡只有冰塊喔？
See if he has ice.
看看他有沒有冰塊
好吧
Hello,Ross?
羅斯
It's Emily here.
我是艾蜜莉
I know this is out of the blue, but I'm getting married tomorrow.
我知道這很突然 但是我明天就要結婚了
Well,maybe I am....
或許啦… 我...
I keep thinking about you.
我一直在想你
And I'm wondering if we made a mistake giving up so fast.
不知道我們太快放棄 是不是一個錯誤
Are you thinking about me?
你有在想我嗎？
No,of course you're not. But if you are,call me tonight.
一定沒有 如果有的話 今晚打給我
Okay, bye.
好吧，再見
Where we going?
下一站是哪裡？
This witness won't return my calls. We'll surprise him coming home.
這個目擊證人不回我電話 我們去他家堵他
Surprise him? We're not gonna make anybody mad,are we?
去堵他？他不會生氣吧？
Come on, man.
得了吧你
You gonna squeeze the perp's shoes a bit before he lawyers up?
那你會在那賊人的律師出現前 先從他身上擠出一些汁來？
He's a witness, not a perp. And no one talks like that.
那是目擊證人，不是賊人 而且沒有人會那樣說話
Yeah. No one talks like that.
是啊，沒人會那樣說話
-Oh,what,like you're Mr. Cop? -I'm more cop than you two.
難不成你是警察？ 我比你們兩個都像警察
How do you figure that?
這是什麼道理？
I'm in the front seat,okay?
醒醒吧，我坐在前座
I'm Gary's partner.
我是蓋瑞的搭檔
When you say "partner," it doesn't sound cop.
你說搭檔的時候不像警察
It sounds gay.
倒像是同志
Jealous.
愛吃醋
-Hey,we're undercover here. -Oh,yeah. No problem.
我們這是秘密出勤 好，沒問題
-Ross! -Sorry.
羅斯 抱歉…
There.
好了
Hey,Gary. Who am l?
蓋瑞，我是誰？
Phone home.
打電話回家
Look at Officer Ross riding back here with the visitors.
看看這位羅斯警官 被打入後座了
What's up with that,Serpico?
是啊，
"What's up with that,Serpico?"
這是怎麼一回事呢？
Are you thinking about me? No,of course you're not.
你有在想我嗎？ 一定沒有
But if you are,call me tonight.
如果有的話，今晚打給我
Okay,bye.
好吧，再見
No.
不會吧
I know!
我知道
Thank God you were here. We have to erase that.
幸好先被你聽到了 我們一定要把這留言洗掉
What? We can't do that.
什麼？我們不能那樣
We have to. What if Ross hears that...
非這樣不可 萬一羅斯聽到了
...and calls her back and they get back together?
回電給她 他們又復合了怎麼辦？
Is that what you want? Ross back with that controlling...
你希望那樣嗎？ 看到羅斯跟那個控制欲超強
...neurotic,crazy Emily? The Emily that wouldn't let him see you?
神經兮兮的瘋子艾蜜莉復合？ 那個不讓羅斯見你的艾蜜莉？
No! Oh,no,no.
不行，萬萬不可…
God,no! He should not get back with her.
羅斯絕對不能和她復合
I know that,you know that. Even Ross knows that.
你知我知，就連羅斯都知道
But we have no right to erase his message.
但我們還是沒有權力 擅自洗掉給羅斯的留言
Look,I'm his sister and I love him. I don't want to see him get hurt.
我可是他的妹妹 我愛他，不想看他受到傷害
Doesn't that give me the right to control him?
得了 我這樣還沒有權控制…
Help him?
幫助他嗎？
He's not the one who needs help.
我覺得需要幫忙的不是他
She's obviously unstable.
艾蜜莉非常不穩定
She's thinking about running out on her wedding day.
她竟然想在結婚當天落跑
Okay,fine. But look at the position she's putting him in.
好啦，但你看看 她讓羅斯陷入了什麼處境
And what's he gonna do?
你要羅斯怎麼辦？
Run over there on the wedding day and break up the marriage?
難不成在艾蜜莉結婚當天 跑去破壞婚禮？
Who would do that?
誰做得出那種事？
Okay,fine. All right. But that was different.
好啦，不過這是兩碼子事
Although it did involve a lot of the same people.
雖然有很多人都是重複的
This is some twisted joke she's playing on him.
艾蜜莉顯然想用變態的笑話 來惡整羅斯
You are crazy. She sounded genuinely upset.
夠了，你瘋了 她聽起來真的很沮喪
I mean,listen.
你聽聽就知道
Your messages have been erased.
您的留言已經清除
No!
不會吧…
Well,that worked out well. Margarita?
這樣就省事多了 來杯瑪格莉特？
Okay,but we're safe, right? Nothing bad's gonna go down.
我們很安全，對吧？ 不可能會有厄運降臨
No. But that reminds me. Sign this.
對，不過我倒想起來了 簽一下這個
What is it?
這是什麼？
It just says you can't sue if you scrape your knee...
沒什麼，只是不能告到市政府頭上 就算斷腿...
...or get your head blown off.
...或者腦袋開花
Oh,hurry up. I want to sign that.
快點喔，我要簽
Here he comes.
好，他來了
What is he doing? What the hell is he doing?
他在幹嘛？搞什麼鬼？
What is it?
什麼？…怎麼了？
-ls everything okay? -What?
沒事吧？ 發生什麼事？
He sees us. Don't move. And don't look at him!
他看到我們了，別動 不要看他
Hey,it's okay. It was just a car backfire.
沒事的，只是車子逆火
Hey, look at that. You tried to save your buddy.
看看，你想用身體掩護朋友
You see that?
你看到了沒？
You see what he did?
看到他冒命拯救朋友沒？
You okay,man?
你沒事吧？
Thanks,Joey.
喬伊，謝了
Hello?
那我呢？
Hi.
嗨
You all right?
沒事吧？
We should go.
我們應該走了
No,wait.
等等…
Oh,yeah. Right.
對，錢拿走
No. Monica.
不是啦，摩妮卡…
Monica,we have to fix this.
摩妮卡，我們得補救這個
What can we do? You erased the message.
我們無能為力啊 你已經把留言洗掉了
Yeah,but maybe I could call his machine and re-create the message.
或許我可以再打電話進來 重新假造一段同樣的留言
All right,okay....
我來試試…
Hello,Ross,this is Rachel Emily.
羅斯，我是瑞秋…艾蜜莉
God,what is it with those two names?
天啊 我怎麼連名字都說不好
I do so wanted to say that I'm going to be getting married...
我打來只是要說我就快要…
...to another British person.
跟另外一個英國人結婚了
And I'm having doubts and scones....
我心裡很疑惑…
-I can't remember what she said. -Yeah,that's the problem with this plan.
我忘記她說了什麼 是啊，計劃的問題就在這裡
Rachel,come on. The message is erased, there's nothing we can do.
瑞秋，留言已經洗掉了 我們無能為力
He's never gonna find out.
羅斯永遠不會發現的
I could tell him about it.
我可以老實跟他說啊
If you want to be rational, I can't argue with you.
如果你想要這麼明理的話 我也爭不過你
All right?
好啦
Fine,tell him. I just don't want to be a part of it.
你要說就說 我不想介入
Maybe that's Emily leaving the exact same message.
或許又是艾蜜莉打來的 她想說一樣的話
Hey,Ross,it's you. I just want you to remember this feeling.
羅斯，是你啊 我只是要你記得這種感覺
You are lucky to be alive.
活著是一種幸運
So live every day to the fullest.
所以每一天都要活得精彩
Love yourself, okay?
珍愛自己，好嗎？
And also get stamps. Bye.
好吧，也別忘了買郵票，再見
Play that message for Emily, and this problem goes away.
只要把這留言放給艾蜜莉聽 所有的問題就都解決了
Right?
是嗎？
Anybody want to meet a hero?
誰要來見見英雄？
John Glenn is here?
約翰葛林來了？
No. Joey.
不，是喬伊
Joey's never been in outer space.
喬伊沒有上過太空啊
We had the most incredible night.
菲比，今晚真是太不可思議了
-We're in the car -Wait. Hold on.
我們在警車裡… 慢著…
-Hi. -Hi.
嗨 嗨
Okay,go ahead.
好，繼續說
So we're in the car,and bang! A shot was fired.
好…我們在警車裡 突然呯一聲 有人開槍
And Joey,with no regard for his own safety...
喬伊完全不顧自己的安危
...throws himself on me.
撲到我身上保護我
My God!
天啊，喬伊
It was a car backfire.
那是汽車逆火放屁的聲音
But he didn't know that.
對，但是當時他並不知道
Yeah,I didn't know that.
對，我不知道
It could just as easily have been a bullet.
那很有可能會是子彈的
Ever think about joining the force? We could use a guy like you.
喬伊，有沒有想過要當警察？ 警界很需要你這種人
Who jumps at loud noises.
聽到巨響就嚇得跳起來
Wow. I could have died tonight.
我今晚有可能喪命的
Yeah,if the car that backfired had run over you!
對，如果那部放屁的車 把你碾過去的話
I'm gonna go home,before Ross starts rambling about his newfound respect for life.
我先回家去了 省得羅斯大談人生新發現
I do have a newfound respect for life.
我的人生的確有了新發現
Oh,my God!
天啊
Ross,I could have told you you weren't gonna die today.
羅斯，我早該跟你說 你今天不會有死劫的
What? You know when I'm gonna die?
你知道我為什麼會死？
-You want to get some dinner? -Sure.
親愛的，你要吃晚餐嗎？ 好啊，當然
You know what? If I heard a shot right now, I'd throw my body on you.
你知道嗎，若現在聽到槍聲 我一定會撲倒你身上
Maybe we should walk in a bad neighborhood.
是嗎？那我們或許應該 去窮兇惡極的社區散步
Okay.
好
Bye.
再見 再見
Cut it out.
羅斯，你別再鬧了
I'd hate to save your life and kick your ass on the same day.
我不想在同一天裡 先是救你又痛扁你一頓
Why'd you take off?
你剛才怎麼先閃了？
Just going for a walk.
我只是去散步
Around the living room,whatever.
在客廳裡繞來繞去
-ls something wrong? -No. No,I'm just tired.
有什麼不對嗎？ 沒有，我只是累了
You know,from the walk.
走路走累了
You dove in front of Ross!
好吧 你撲上去救羅斯
Ross!
羅斯耶！
That's what this is about.
原來是這麼一回事
Oh,my God. You hate Ross!
天啊，你恨羅斯
I don't hate Ross.
我沒有恨羅斯
Of course you do. I saved him. You're mad at me. It adds up.
你當然有！ 我救了他，你生我的氣 這樣全都說得通了
You want Ross out of the picture.
你想剷除羅斯？
What picture?
剷除什麼？
I don't know. But I don't like what I'm hearing.
不知道，但是你說的話很嚇人
I'm glad you saved Ross in the car backfire. But it could've been a bullet.
我很高興你在汽車放屁事件中 救了羅斯一命 但那若真的是子彈怎麼辦？
And you didn't try to save me.
你竟然救他不救我
You're upset because you think I chose Ross over you.
原來你是在氣這個 你以為我覺得羅斯比你重要
No,I knew you could take care of yourself.
不是這樣的… 我知道你能照顧自己
You know? I mean,Ross needs help. He's not "street" like us.
羅斯需要別人幫忙 他不像你我見過大場面
You'd risk your life for Ross before you would for me.
話說到頭，你寧願先去救羅斯 也不來救我
That's the bottom line.
這才是重點
No,not exactly.
不完全是這樣
All right,look.
好吧，好吧
I wasn't trying to save Ross.
其實我那不是要救羅斯
Okay?
My sandwich was next to Ross.
我的三明治在羅斯旁邊
All right?
I was trying to save my sandwich.
我是要救我的三明治
From a bullet?
怕它被槍打到？
-I know it doesn't make much sense. -"Much" sense?
我知道這說來沒啥道理… 豈止沒啥道理
Look,it was instinct! I just went for it.
錢德，那是本能反應 當下就撲過去了
You risked your life for a sandwich?
所以你冒命去救三明治
I know it sounds crazy...
我知道這聽起來很誇張
...but this is the greatest sandwich in the world!
但這可是世界上最棒的三明治
So you didn't choose Ross before me?
所以你並不覺得羅斯比我重要
No. I would never do that.
是啊，我絕對不會那樣
You're like my brother.
你就像是我的親兄弟
-Really? -Yeah.
真的？ 對
In fact,to prove how much you mean to me....
為了證明你對我的意義
Here.
給你
-Thanks. -Easy, it's not a hot dog!
謝了 輕一點，這不是熱狗
How good is that?
是不是很好吃？
See?
看吧
What are you doing?
慢著，你在幹嘛？
You're showing me how much I mean to you.
你不是要證明我對你的意義？
With a bite.
是啊，咬一口來證明
Jeez!
你也幫幫忙
嗨
What are you doing here?
瑞秋，你在這裡幹嘛？
Hey,you know what?
You are in our apartment all the time!
你動不動就往我們的公寓跑
This is just a drop in the bucket,mister!
我這只是小巫見大巫而已
It doesn't matter. The important thing is that you're here.
沒關係啦，重點是你來了
You're my friend and you're here.
你是我朋友，而你來到了這裡
Okay,just a little scared. What's going on?
好，我有一點點害怕 羅斯，你是怎麼了？
The most amazing thing happened tonight.
今晚發生了最不尋常的事
I thought my number was up.
我還以為自己要去見閻王了
I had an actual near-death experience.
我真正面臨到了瀕死經驗
What happened?
什麼？…怎麼回事？
We were on the ride-along with Gary and somebody took a shot at me!
我們不是跟蓋瑞 坐警車兜風嗎？ 有人朝我開槍！
Really?
真的嗎？
No. A car backfired.
不是，是車子放屁
But I thought somebody was taking a shot at me. And,Rach...
但我當時以為是有人對我開槍 瑞秋
...I survived!
我劫後餘生
And I was filled with this great respect for life.
我的人生擁有了全新視野
I want to experience every moment.
我要真切體驗每一刻
I want to seize every opportunity.
我要把握每一個機會
I am seeing everything so clearly now.
現在的一切都變得好清晰
Because a car backfired?
全都是因為汽車放屁？
Okay. Why are you here?
好吧，你來這裡幹嘛？
I don't know how this fits into your whole "seizing" thing...
我不知道這件事符不符合 你所謂的「把握今朝」
...but Emily called you today.
不過艾蜜莉今天打了電話給你
-You talked to her? -She left a message.
你跟她說了話？ 沒有，她在你電話裡留言
But it kind of got erased.
不過留言被洗掉了
I mean,there's something wrong with your machine.
你的答錄機有問題
What did she say?
那她說了什麼？
Something about having second thoughts about the wedding...
說什麼對結婚的事有點反悔
...and did you guys make a mistake breaking up?
說你們分手是個錯誤
And she wants you to call her.
她要你回電
Wow.
That was a good thing that I told you, right?
我跟你說這件事很對吧？
Yeah. Yes. Of course.
是啊，當然是這樣
Okay,thank you. Thank you. Because
謝謝你… 謝謝 因為...
I'm gonna go tell Monica I was right.
我要去跟摩妮卡說 我這樣做是對的
Because she didn't want
因為你知道嗎？她不希望…
Not important. Point is, I was right. Your decision.
那不重要 重點是我是對的，你自己決定
Okay?
I was right.
我是對的
Your decision.
你自己決定要不要回電
Right.
對
I guess I should call Emily.
我猜我應該回電給艾蜜莉
No, that's not the right decision.
不對，你的決定不對…
That's not right.
這樣不對
Ross,come on!
羅斯，你清醒一點
I mean...
我是說...
...that woman made you miserable!
...那個女人把你給整慘了
Do you really want to get back into that?
羅斯，你真的想要再來一次？
Okay,look. Yesterday...
如果她是在昨天打來的
...I wouldn't have even considered calling her back.
我壓根不會想回電
But my ex-wife calls on the same day...
但在我面對瀕死經驗的同一天
...I have a near-death experience?
我的前妻正好打電話來
That's gotta mean something.
這一定有所含意
That was not a near-death experience. That was barely an experience.
羅斯，那不是瀕死經驗 就連經驗都談不上了
You weren't there!
當時你並不在場
Maybe this is something that I'm supposed to seize, you know?
或許這就是我應該把握的事
Okay. You know what?
好吧，你知道嗎？
Maybe this is not about seizing stuff.
或許這無關把握或是不把握
Maybe this is about escaping stuff.
或許這是關於逃避
Okay? Look at today.
就拿今天來說
I mean,you escaped...
你逃過了…
...death.
死忘
And maybe this is a chance for you to escape...
或許這是你逃避機會
...getting back together with Emily.
不去和艾蜜莉復合
That does make sense.
這還蠻有道理的
Because I do want to seize some opportunity...
因為我要把握住這個機會
...but I really don't want to see or talk to her.
不和她見面或聯絡
Well,there you go!
這不就結了
Yeah,maybe today's just...
或許今天只是...
..."close call" day.
...「千鈞一髮」日
Hey, thanks, Rach.
瑞秋，謝了
Oh, honey. No problem.
親愛的，甭客氣
Wait, wait. The message is blinking.
等等…留言燈號在閃
Maybe you didn't erase it.
或許留言沒被洗掉
Hey,Ross,it's you
羅斯，是你啊
That's an old message. Nobody needs to hear that.
這是舊的留言 沒什麼好聽的 沒錯
-Hey,was Monica here? -Yeah.
摩妮卡有來過嗎？ 有啊
I want my money back.
要她把我的錢還來
You probably need that for stamps, right?
是要用來買郵票的吧？
Has Gary ever been shot at for real?
菲比，蓋瑞有真的中槍過嗎？
Yes,once.
有，一次
A little.
小小的一次
He kind of did it to himself.
算是他自己打的
It's not really a good story.
這故事沒什麼好講的
I wonder how I'd react under fire. And not backfire...
不知道我置身戰火會怎樣 不是汽車放屁
...but heavy fire.
是槍林彈雨
Like,if I was in a war.
好比我在戰場上之類的
Man,I would be great in a war!
我去打仗一定很厲害
I think I'd make a fantastic military leader.
一定會是很棒的軍事領袖
I mean,I know I'd make general before any of you guys.
跟你們這些人比起來 我一定會最先當上將軍
Before or after you were shot by your own troops?
在你被自己的部下槍殺前 還是之後？
I know Joey would be in the foxhole protecting all of us.
我知道喬伊一定會在散兵坑裡保護大家
If the foxhole was lined with sandwiches.
對，如果那個散兵坑 是用三明治圍起來的話
Yeah, hero sandwiches.
沒錯，英雄三明治
You all know I'm a pacifist, so I'm not interested in war in any way.
你們知道我主張和平 我對什麼戰爭都沒興趣
But when the revolution comes, I'll have to destroy you all.
不過等到革命的那一天來臨 我一定要把你們消滅光光
Not you, Joey.
喬伊，你例外